<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>HomePage on Ayham's Online Website</title><link>https://ayham.xyz/</link><description>Recent content in HomePage on Ayham's Online Website</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>me@ayham.xyz (ayham)</managingEditor><webMaster>me@ayham.xyz (ayham)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 13:30:24 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ayham.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Library</title><link>https://ayham.xyz/library/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 20:56:50 +0300</pubDate><author>me@ayham.xyz (ayham)</author><guid>https://ayham.xyz/library/</guid><description>List of books I read, this is neither a recommendation list nor endorsement.
Theodore Kaczynski - Technological Slavery Bronze Age Pervert - Bronze Age Mindset Anne Rooney - Think Like A Mathematician Charles Darwin - A Tale Of Two Cities George Orwell - 1984
Christopher Marlowe - Dr. Faustus John Steinback - The Winter of Our Discontent John Steinback - Of Mice and Men Ph.d. Robert P. Murphy - The Politically Incorrect Guide to Capitalism George Orwell - Animal Farm Nassim Nicholas Taleb - Skin in the Game John R.</description></item><item><title>A Minimal Linux Display Manager</title><link>https://ayham.xyz/posts/a-minimal-linux-display-manager/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 13:30:24 +0300</pubDate><author>me@ayham.xyz (ayham)</author><guid>https://ayham.xyz/posts/a-minimal-linux-display-manager/</guid><description>&lt;p>There is this itch that tiling window manager users feel. Whether it is caused
by surfing the world of r/unix or the want for change, it might be useful to
have a way to easily switch between window managers. This article shows how to
achieve this using already installed applications on your system.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>blogit: A Complete Guide</title><link>https://ayham.xyz/posts/blogit-to-blog-it/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 13:30:24 +0300</pubDate><author>me@ayham.xyz (ayham)</author><guid>https://ayham.xyz/posts/blogit-to-blog-it/</guid><description>&lt;p>Running a personal website should be an easy task. Unfortunately, a big
hindrance is that there aren&amp;rsquo;t many &amp;ldquo;suckless&amp;rdquo; blogging system.
&lt;a href="https://pedantic.software/git/blogit"target="_blank">blogit&lt;/a>&lt;span class="externalLink">🔗&lt;/span> is the closest in terms of
simplicity and minimalism to perfection. This article would be an end-all be-all
guide to effectively install blogit onto your own website.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Eid Marks Calculator</title><link>https://ayham.xyz/apps/eid.marks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 13:30:24 +0300</pubDate><author>me@ayham.xyz (ayham)</author><guid>https://ayham.xyz/apps/eid.marks/</guid><description>&lt;p>This is a very simple eid marks calculator where you put your subject marks,
press calculate and pray for the best!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hardening The Moto One Macro</title><link>https://ayham.xyz/posts/hardening-the-one-macro/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 13:30:24 +0300</pubDate><author>me@ayham.xyz (ayham)</author><guid>https://ayham.xyz/posts/hardening-the-one-macro/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Motorola One Macro is a mid-range phone, with decent &amp;ldquo;openness&amp;rdquo; which allows
basic hardening modification. The phone has the follow specifications:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Mediatek MT6771 Helio P70 CPU&lt;/li>
&lt;li>720 x 1520 px, 19:9 ratios (~270 ppi)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Comes with Anroid 9.0, officially upgradable to Android 10.0&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Mali-G72 MP3 GPU&lt;/li>
&lt;li>eMMC 5.1 storage with 64GB&lt;/li>
&lt;li>microSDXC uses shared SIM slot, 32GB tested&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Main camera 13 MP, depth camera 2MP, 2MP for macro camera&lt;/li>
&lt;li>WIFI 802.11 b/g/n, with hotspot&lt;/li>
&lt;li>No NFC support&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>This guide goes over unlocking the bootloader, flashing a GSI, flashing
LineageOS, reflashing stock ROM, fixing bootloop problems, and news
on TWRP for the Moto One Macro.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Morality Of Pursuing Money: An Essay</title><link>https://ayham.xyz/posts/morality-of-pursuing-money-an-essay/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 13:30:24 +0300</pubDate><author>me@ayham.xyz (ayham)</author><guid>https://ayham.xyz/posts/morality-of-pursuing-money-an-essay/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;em>The following is an essay from an assignment task in school that I took too
seriously. After contemplation, I realize that the essay itself is not complete
and probably contains linguistic mistakes. However, this is AN attempt at
rationalizing money pursuit. While developing the argument presented here, I had
a debate with a classmate which helped write the intent section. All ideas
presented here are just ideas and nothing serious.&lt;/em>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Beginning of a series!</title><link>https://ayham.xyz/posts/firstpost/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 13:30:24 +0300</pubDate><author>me@ayham.xyz (ayham)</author><guid>https://ayham.xyz/posts/firstpost/</guid><description>The Beginning of a series!
This would be the beginning of my all-new article series. I would be writing about software I make and use, with the occasional school essay turned article.
The story shall begin!</description></item><item><title>True Full Disk Encryption On Linux</title><link>https://ayham.xyz/posts/true-full-disk-encryption/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 13:30:24 +0300</pubDate><author>me@ayham.xyz (ayham)</author><guid>https://ayham.xyz/posts/true-full-disk-encryption/</guid><description>&lt;p>My friends laugh at me when they are told that I have to put in 4 passwords
with ~18 characters each to login into my computer. I laugh back at them,
wishing them joy with Ads in the start-menu.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In this article, we will discuss &lt;em>true&lt;/em> full disk encryption. Everything,
including having the kernel encrypted using LUKS. I personally found difficulty
in finding good documentation detailing how to set-up disk encryption.
Hopefully this guide would help someone out there.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Website's Details</title><link>https://ayham.xyz/details/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 13:30:24 +0300</pubDate><author>me@ayham.xyz (ayham)</author><guid>https://ayham.xyz/details/</guid><description>If you have stumbled upon this page, chances are you want to know how this works. This website is built using https://gohugo.io🔗. The project can be found here on Github🔗.
All pages use no cookies, except stated otherwise. All external links are marked with a link emoji. Specific WASM binaries for applications hosted can be found on their respective websites. All linked resources include an integrity attribute. All linked resources are minified where possible, check project for full code.</description></item></channel></rss>